It's done, let me show you
what all has happened in the student, see this has been delayed,
and look at the break on the
right side next to the like, and see this, if you keep the entire scratch in
front, it will
not cost you any money and whatever
problem you have will be solved, it will only cost you
money and you can see I have completed it
[music] If
you are a student, do
not make a small insurance claim, otherwise
you might have a problem, you
can apply later, the insurance will be reduced a
little, for students you can make a new claim,
for this you can talk to Ola care,
if it can be fixed in less money, then you can get it done, you can
visit the Ola centre and check, there is a
small scratch,
I had made a claim for this but I will take it
back because there is a small
scratch, I could not see that much, so you should buy
Ola wisely, Ola car is fine but
its service charges are very high, then
you can take Ola Plus, if you live far away then you can
see, through
which whatever service you
can get, but that too will cost you money, if we
slip in water then drive slowly
and this is how it will happen